ikoo.com 2014-12-31

# Privacy Policy

ikoo.com (together with its subsidiaries and affiliates, "ikoo"), respects the privacy and security of its customers and users of its website and services. ikoo strives to provide you with a personalized internet experience that delivers to you the information, products and services that you need. In order to achieve this goal, ikoo sometimes collects information during your visits to our website. We will not disclose this information to any person or organization outside ikoo, except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

We have prepared this Privacy Policy to enable you to understand which personal identifying information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information We Collect**  
ikoo collects certain information from and about its users three ways: (i) from our web server logs, (ii) with cookies & pixel tags and (iii) directly from the user. **  
**

**Web server logs:**   
When you visit our website, ikoo may collect information to administer the site and analyze its usage. ikoo may collect information such as:   
**-** your Internet protocol address ;   
**-** the type of browser or computer you use;   
**-** the number of links you click within our website;   
**-** the state or country from which you accessed our website;   
**-** the date and time of your visit;   
**-** the name of your Internet service provider;   
**-** the Web page from which you linked to our website; and   
**-** the pages you viewed on our website

**Cookies & Pixel Tags  
**

ikoo uses ZEDO as its adserving technology partner, ikoo may collects anonymous information through the use of cookies and pixel tags, which are industry standard technologies used by many major Web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. For more details on how to opt out please visit ZEDO's privacy policy page at:   
**<http://www.zedo.com/company/privacy.htm> ****  
**

Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer: A cookie file simply contains a string of alphanumeric characters, which is passed from a Web site to your computer and back to the Web site, unchanged, for recognition purposes. Web sites use cookies to recognize a computer that has previously visited the site or page. Cookies are often wrongly categorized as 'Spyware', or as a virus or other malicious program. A cookie itself cannot do anything except help a Web site behave in a manner customized to you.

ikoo uses cookies to enhance the Web experience by preventing users from seeing the same Internet ad over and over again. ikoo does not use cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies cannot damage your system or files.  
You can tell your browser to accept or reject cookies for all sites, or for specific sites; but remember, rejecting cookies may affect the way your favorite sites behave.

To make certain that ads served by ikoo are targeted correctly, we may place pixel tags on our sites. These tags are not personally identifiable, nor do they collect personal information. They are used to match visitor browsing behavior to a segment profile designated for targeting ads to visitors.  
When you are on one of our customer's Web sites (including advertisers and Web site owners), the Web site uses cookies to collect certain non-personal information about you, including but not limited to: your browser type (Internet Explorer, Mozilla, etc.); operating system (Windows, Macintosh, etc.); your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the site, the content areas or pages of the site you visit (for example, 'auto section' or 'entertainment section'), ads clicked on and other click-stream data. None of this data contains personal information about you.

**Personal information users give us:**  
On some pages of our website, users may fill forms to contact ikoo support & sales or send an application to join our network. When you fill any of those forms, ikoo may ask you for some personal information.

If you're purchasing products or services, we may also request financial information such as credit card or bank account information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the products and services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number. We may then contact you with information about ikoo's products and services.

As a security measure and to ensure that our website and computer network remain available to all customers, ikoo may use software programs to monitor network traffic or to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. These software programs may also collect information regarding your use of our website and computer network.

You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide technical support assistance and information to you. For example, we may collect personal information from you (such as an e-mail address, system information and problem descriptions) in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. If you choose to correspond with us through electronic communication (e.g. email, online chat or instant messaging), we may retain a copy of the electronic communication together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

Finally, some pages of ikoo's website may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups or instant messaging available to you. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Don't disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential – such as financial information, social security numbers, passwords or email addresses. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas, that information and any substantive information disclosed in the communication can be collected and used by third parties. This could result in unsolicited messages from others who post on such sites and are beyond the control of ikoo.

**How We Use Your Information  
** ikoo uses the anonymous information it collects to customize the advertisements that consumers see on participating Web sites and to analyze if the advertising resulted in a desired action, such as a sale. This is sometimes referred to as Online Preference Marketing (OPM) or Behavioral Targeting. In order to serve appropriate ads to visitors, ikoo will temporarily assemble non-personal behavioral and technical information to create very large audience segments. These segments represent data that has been aggregated into large anonymous groupings.  
ikoo stores all anonymous, non PII data in user cookies and not on any servers. These cookies have a lifetime of one year and can be blocked or deleted by users using the methods described on our Opt Out page. [**Click here to opt out**](http://www.ikoo.com/index.php/en/Opt-Out).

ikoo may also use the information we collect to notify you about your account and to notify you about changes to the terms and conditions governing your use of our website, products and services. We may also use the information we collect to notify you about other products and services we think you will find valuable and about special offers. You may notify us of your desire not to receive notifications relating to new products and services and special offers by "opting-out" as provided for below.

ikoo may also provide aggregate information about our customers, this website's traffic patterns and related website usage information to our affiliates and reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford similar privacy protections to their customers. However, we do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.

**Disclosure of Information**  
ikoo does not provide any personal information to marketers when you interact with or view a targeted ad. The user information that we collect to create segments and profile information for our service is not shared with any other outside party. At the same time, our advertiser customers cannot correlate or merge any network segment information that they may collect process or store in connection with their site, including such personal information except in compliance with the applicable customer contracts and such customer's privacy policy. PII may be utilized by advertiser customers at a later time, as part of their customer relationship management (CRM) programs, for example.  
**Opting Out**  
If you do not want to store this information in your browser, you can easily deny, or opt out of, cookies. There is more than one way to opt out of cookies: manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the "Help" section of your browser; or, [**go to our Opt Out page**](http://www.ikoo.com/index.php/en/Opt-Out) and click the "Opt Out Now" button provided. We will no longer deliver ads targeted to your preferences and usage patterns.  
**The ikoo Opt-out Tool is cookie-based**. In order for the Tool to work on your computer, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. If you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete this cookie, you will need to perform the opt-out task again.

**How We Protect Your Information**  
ikoo uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control.

When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. However, please note that electronic communication (e.g. email, online chat or instant messaging) that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you in advance that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as financial information, social security numbers or passwords to us through unsecured electronic communication.

**Access to Your Information**  
ikoo will share or disclosure your personal data in four ways:   
**-** as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, or as compelled by a court of law;   
**-** with other affiliates or partners of ikoo (as described above);   
**-** with agents and contractors who use such information on behalf of ikoo or in connection with administering or delivering products and services on behalf of ikoo; and   
**-** as needed in connection with the transfer of business assets.

**Links to Other Websites**  
ikoo's website contain links to sites maintained by other companies that are not affiliated with ikoo. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites, and we encourage you to use caution when visiting them. In particular, we recommend you view the privacy policy posted on each site.

**How to Correct Inaccuracies**  
you may contact us at [****](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy31221%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy31221%20=%20addy31221%20+%20'ikoo'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy31221%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy31221%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)**[info@ikoo.com](mailto:info@ikoo.com)**

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
ikoo hereby reserves the right to amend, alter, modify, replace or suspend this Privacy Policy, from time to time, in its sole discretion. All such changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted on ikoo's website.

**Questions**  
If you have any comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact ikoo via email at[ ** **](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy26846%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy26846%20=%20addy26846%20+%20'ikoo'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy26846%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy26846%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)**[info@ikoo.com](mailto:info@ikoo.com)**
